{"data":{"site":{"pathPrefix":"/restaurant-inspections"},"postgres":{"establishment":[{"establishmentid":"514","name":"Taqueria Mi Pueblo","address":"7278 Dix Ave","zipcode":"48209","owner":"Jose Jesus Lopez","licenseNumber":"034343","licenseType":"Fixed Establishment","establishmentType":"Food Service Establishment","establishmentStatus":"Open","riskCategory":null,"reviewFrequencyDays":"180","coords":"-83.12416,42.31715","geojson":{"id":"514","type":"Feature","geometry":{"type":"Point","coordinates":[-83.124161643,42.317150466]},"properties":{"name":"Taqueria Mi Pueblo","owner":"Jose Jesus Lopez","address":"7278 Dix Ave","zipcode":"48209","license_type":"Fixed Establishment","risk_category":null,"license_number":"034343","establishmentid":"514","establishment_type":"Food Service Establishment","establishment_status":"Open","review_frequency_days":"180","most_recent_license_date":"4/15/2019"}},"nearbyList":[{"establishmentid":"3849","name":"El Kiosko","address":"7271 Dix Ave","zipcode":"48209"},{"establishmentid":"51622476","name":"Mi Pueblo Express","address":"7271 Dix Ave","zipcode":"48209"},{"establishmentid":"3858","name":"Pollos Los Gallos","address":"7135 Dix Ave","zipcode":"48209"},{"establishmentid":"5223","name":"Primo's Tacos","address":"7643 Dix Ave","zipcode":"48216"},{"establishmentid":"1015","name":"Casey's Bar L.L.C.","address":"7677 Dix Ave","zipcode":"48209"},{"establishmentid":"995","name":"Harms School Elementary","address":"2400 Central Ave","zipcode":"48209"},{"establishmentid":"201","name":"Taqueria El Nacimiento","address":"7400 W Vernor","zipcode":"48209"},{"establishmentid":"1342","name":"Restaurant Nuestra Familia","address":"7620 W Vernor","zipcode":"48209"},{"establishmentid":"1494","name":"J & J Coney Island #3","address":"7220 W Vernor","zipcode":"48209"},{"establishmentid":"4358","name":"Domino's Pizza","address":"7603 W Vernor","zipcode":"48209"}],"inspectionsByEstablishmentidList":[{"inspectionid":"49437","inspectionDate":"2019-10-10T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"4-501.116","violationDescription":"Concentration of the SANITIZING solution shall be accurately determined by using a test kit or other device. (Pf)\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Sanitizer test kit","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not used","subProblem":"","location":"DISH MACHINE","subLocation":"Test strips","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2019-11-07T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Use test kit to verify sanitizer concentration."},{"violationCode":"4-501.112","violationDescription":"In a mechanical operation, the temperature of the fresh hot water SANITIZING rinse as it enters the manifold may not be more than 194 F, or less than 165 F for stationary rack machines or 180 F for all other machines to assure proper sanitizing of utensils. (Pf)\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Dish machine final rinse temperature","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Less than 180 degrees F","subProblem":"","location":"DISH MACHINE","subLocation":"SANITIZING","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2019-10-10T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Repair to provide temperature stated above."},{"violationCode":"3-304.12","violationDescription":"During pauses in FOOD preparation or dispensing, UTENSILS shall be stored:\r\n(A) In the FOOD with their handles above the top of the FOOD and the container;\r\n(B) In FOOD that is not POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS with their handles above the      top of the FOOD within containers or EQUIPMENT that can be closed, such as      bins of sugar, flour, or cinnamon;\r\n(C) On a clean portion of the FOOD preparation table or cooking EQUIPMENT\r\n(D)  In running water, such as dipper well.\r\n(E)  In a clean, protected location if the UTENSILS, such as ice scoops, are   used only with a FOOD that is not POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS; or\r\n(F)  In a container of water maintained at a temperature of at least 135° F.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Dispensing utensil(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Improperly stored","subProblem":"With handle in product","location":"WAITRESS STATION","subLocation":"Dispensing utensil","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Relocate."},{"violationCode":"5-205.15","violationDescription":"A PLUMBING SYSTEM shall be:\r\n(A) Repaired according to LAW; (P) and\r\n(B) Maintained in good repair.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Plumbing system","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not maintained","subProblem":"","location":"PLUMBING","subLocation":"Water lines","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Maintain in good repair"}]},{"inspectionid":"45858","inspectionDate":"2019-04-10T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"3-302.11","violationDescription":"(A) FOOD shall be protected from cross contamination by:  \r\n(1) Except as specified in (1)(c) below, separating raw animal FOODS during         storage, preparation, holding, and display from:\r\n(a) Raw READY-TO-EAT FOOD including other raw animal FOOD such as FISH for sushi or MOLLUSCAN SHELLFISH, or other raw READY-TO-EAT FOOD such as fruits and vegetables,(P) and\r\n(b) Cooked READY-TO-EAT FOOD; (P)\r\n(c) Frozen, commercially processed and packaged raw animal FOOD may be          stored or displayed with or above frozen, commercially processed and           packaged, ready-to-eat food.\r\n(2) Except when combined as ingredients, separating types of raw animal FOODS    from each other such as beef, FISH, lamb, pork, and POULTRY during storage,        preparation, holding, and display by:\r\n(a) Using separate EQUIPMENT for each type, (P) or\r\n(b) Arranging each type of FOOD in EQUIPMENT so that cross contamination of one type with another is prevented, (P) and\r\n(c) Preparing each type of FOOD at different times or in separate areas; (P)\r\n","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":"Raw animal food(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Stored over/next to","subProblem":"","location":"WALK-IN COOLER","subLocation":"Food Storage","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2019-04-24T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Store raw animal foods below and away from foods needing little or no further prep."},{"violationCode":"5-203.14","violationDescription":"A PLUMBING SYSTEM shall be installed to preclude backflow of contaminants into the water supply system at each point of use at the FOOD ESTABLISHMENT by providing an air gap or installing an APPROVED backflow prevention device. (P)\r\n","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":"Backflow prevention","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"","location":"DISH ROOM","subLocation":"BACK FLOW PREVENTER","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2019-04-24T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide."},{"violationCode":"6-301.12","violationDescription":"Each HANDWASHING SINK or group of adjacent HANDWASHING SINKS shall be provided with:\r\n(A) Individual, disposable towels; (Pf)\r\n(B) A continuous towel system that supplies the user with a clean towel;(Pf) or \r\n(C) A heated-air hand drying device.(Pf)\r\n(D) A hand drying device that employs an air-knife system that delivers high velocity pressurized air at ambient temperatures.(Pf)\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Sanitary hand drying provisions","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"Handsink","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2019-04-10T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide."},{"violationCode":"4-203.12","violationDescription":"(A)     Ambient air and water TEMPERATURE MEASURING DEVICES that are scaled in Celsius or dually scaled in Celsius and Fahrenheit shall be designed to be easily readable and accurate to ±1.5C in the intended range of use. (Pf)\r\n(B)     Ambient air and water TEMPERATURE MEASURING DEVICES that are scaled only in Fahrenheit shall be accurate to 3F in the intended range of use. (Pf)\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Air/water thermometer(s)","subItem":"cooler(s) reach in","problemDescription":"Not accurate","subProblem":"","location":"COOLER","subLocation":"Thermometer(s)","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2019-04-24T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Replace."},{"violationCode":"5-501.17","violationDescription":"A toilet room used by females shall be provided with a covered receptacle for sanitary napkins.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Covered waste receptacle(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"","location":"RESTROOM (WOMEN'S) EMPLOYEE)","subLocation":"Covered waste container","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":"2019-04-24T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide."},{"violationCode":"3-305.12","violationDescription":"FOOD may not be stored:\r\n(A)  In locker rooms;\r\n(B)  In toilet rooms;\r\n(C)  In dressing rooms;\r\n(D)  In garbage rooms;\r\n(E)  In mechanical rooms;\r\n(F)  Under sewer lines that are not shielded to intercept potential drips;\r\n(G)  Under leaking water lines, including leaking automatic fire sprinkler heads, or        under lines on which water has condensed;\r\n(H)  Under open stairwells; or\r\n(I)   Under other sources of contamination.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Food(s) stored","subItem":"","problemDescription":"In prohibited area(s)","subProblem":"In or under other sources of contamination","location":"ESTABLISHMENT","subLocation":"Food Storage","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Store in protected manner."},{"violationCode":"6-202.13","violationDescription":"Insect control devices that are used to electrocute or stun flying insects shall be designed to retain the insect within the device, shall not be located over a FOOD preparation area, and prevent contamination of  exposed FOOD; clean EQUIPMENT,UTENSILS, and LINENS; and unwrapped SINGLE-SERVICE and SINGLE-USE ARTICLES.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Insect control device(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Located over preparation area","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"Pest Control Device","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":"2019-04-10T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Move to eliminate potential contamination."}]},{"inspectionid":"44088","inspectionDate":"2018-11-08T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"No","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"2-301.14","violationDescription":"FOOD EMPLOYEES shall clean their hands and exposed portions of their arms as specified under § 2-301.12 immediately before engaging in FOOD preparation including working with exposed FOOD, clean EQUIPMENT and UTENSILS, and unwrapped SINGLE-SERVICE and SINGLE-USE ARTICLES (P) and:\r\n(A)     After touching bare human body parts other than clean hands and clean, exposed portions of arms; (P)\r\n(B)     After using the toilet room; (P)\r\n(C)     After caring for or handling SERVICE ANIMALS or aquatic animals as specified in ¶ 2-403.11(B); (P).\r\n(D)     Except as specified in ¶ 2-401.11(B), after coughing, sneezing, using a handkerchief or disposable tissue, using tobacco, eating, or drinking; (P)\r\n(E)     After handling soiled EQUIPMENT or UTENSILS; (P)\r\n(F)     During FOOD preparation, as often as necessary to remove soil and contamination and to prevent cross contamination when changing tasks; (P)\r\n(G)     When switching between working with raw FOOD and working with READY-TO-EAT FOOD; (P)\r\n(H)     Before donning gloves for working with FOOD; (P) and\r\n(I)      After engaging in other activities that contaminate the hands. (P)","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":"Employee(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Did not wash hands","subProblem":"","location":"GRILL AREA","subLocation":"","corrected":"No","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Hands shall be washed with hot water and soap for at least 20 seconds after contamination."},{"violationCode":"3-304.15","violationDescription":"(A) SINGLE-USE gloves shall be used for one task only and discarded when      damaged, soiled, or when interruptions occur in the operation. (P)\r\n\r\n(B) Slash-resistant and cloth gloves shall be used in direct contact only with FOOD that is subsequently cooked. Gloves used with ready-to-eat foods shall be smooth,   durable and non-absorbant.\r\n","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":"Single-use glove(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Used for multiple purposes","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"","corrected":"No","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Gloves shall only be used for one purpose and then disposed."},{"violationCode":"3-301.11","violationDescription":"(A) To prevent food contamination FOOD EMPLOYEES shall properly wash their      hands.\r\n(B) FOOD EMPLOYEES may not contact exposed, READY-TO-EAT FOOD with      their bare hands and shall use suitable UTENSILS such as deli tissue,       spatulas, tongs, single-use gloves, or dispensing EQUIPMENT. (P)\r\n(C) FOOD EMPLOYEES shall minimize bare hand and arm contact with exposed     FOOD that is not in a READY-TO-EAT form. (Pf)\r\n\r\n","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":"Ready-to-eat food(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Handled with bare hands","subProblem":"","location":"BAR","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2018-11-08T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Suitable utensils or single-use gloves are to be utilized."}]},{"inspectionid":"41747","inspectionDate":"2018-03-15T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"5-202.13","violationDescription":"An air gap between the water supply inlet and the flood level rim of the PLUMBING FIXTURE, EQUIPMENT, or nonFOOD EQUIPMENT shall be at least twice the diameter of the water supply inlet and may not be less than 1 inch. (P)\r\n","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":"Air gap","subItem":"between supply line and flood rim of plumbing fixture","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"","location":"BASEMENT","subLocation":"At the Over head spray unit ","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2018-03-15T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide air gap that is twice the diameter of the drain line and no less than 1 inch."}]},{"inspectionid":"39378","inspectionDate":"2017-07-25T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"No","violationsByInspectionidList":[]},{"inspectionid":"37398","inspectionDate":"2016-12-14T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"No","violationsByInspectionidList":[]}]}],"maxInspectionDate":[{"inspectionDate":"2020-10-30T00:00:00"}]}},"pageContext":{"eid":"514"}}